Finding Aid for the Los Angeles Daily News Negatives, 1925-1954
UCLA Library Special Collections
Los Angeles Daily News Negatives,
1925-1954
1387
Los Angeles Daily News
301 boxes (150.5 linear ft.)
The Los Angeles daily news was originally named the Illustrated Daily News by Cornelius Vanderbilt, Jr. when he started it in 1923. He copied the tabloid format of the New York daily news, although he rejected lurid and sensational journalism. In 1926 the paper went bankrupt and was taken over by Manchester Boddy, who changed the name to the Los Angeles daily news. He kept the tabloid format, with its heavy reliance on photographs. In 1954 it merged with the Mirror, the afternoon paper of the Los Angeles times, and became the Mirror-News. It lost reporters, columnists, and its more liberal flavor, and ceased publication in the early 1960s. The collection consists of 200,000 negatives of the Los Angeles Daily News.
University of California, Los Angeles. Library Special Collections. Los Angeles, California 90095-1575
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Advance notice required for access.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of The Times-Mirror Company, 1958.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 4233334
Biography
The Los Angeles daily news was originally named the Illustrated daily news by Cornelius Vanderbilt, Jr. when he started it in 1923. He copied the tabloid format of the New York daily news, although he rejected lurid and sensational journalism. In 1926 the paper went bankrupt and was taken over by Manchester Boddy, who changed the name to the Los Angeles daily news. He kept the tabloid format, with its heavy reliance on photographs. In 1954 it merged with the Mirror, the afternoon paper of the Los Angeles times, and became the Mirror-News. It lost reporters, columnists, and its more liberal flavor, and ceased publication in the early 1960s.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of 200,000 negatives of the Los Angeles daily news.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Negatives (Boxes 1-197, 254-301).
Glass negatives (Boxes 198-253).
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects
Los Angeles daily news--Archives.; American newspapers--California--Los Angeles--Archival resources.
Genres and Forms of Material
Black-and-white negatives.
Items Removed from Collection
20,000 (a 10% sample) of these negatives were printed and indexed to form Collection 1386. Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library.
Related Material
Los Angeles Daily News Records (Collection 1208). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library.
Los Angeles Daily News Photographs (Collection 1386). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library.
Container List
- undated
  - Returning evacuated Japanese Americans, undated; Neg. # 35934-7 (Box 86)
- 1936
  - Los Angeles slums in the Great Depression, ca. 1936; Neg. # 16314-11 (Box 8)
  - Los Angeles slums in the Great Depression, ca. 1936; Neg. # 16314-7 (Box 8)
- 1937
  - Father Divine's Peace Mission and Truth Center expansion, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1937; Neg. # 14359 (Box 5)
  - Father Divine's Peace Mission and Truth Center, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1937; Neg. # 14359-1 (Box 5)
  - Henry Armstrong and his family, ca. 1937; Neg. # 16392-2 (Box 8)
- 1938
  - Henry Armstrong and his manager in the boxing ring, 1938; Neg. # 17212 (Box 10)
  - Los Angeles slums in the Great Depression, ca. 1938; Neg. # 17527-1 (Box 10)
  - Raid on a Chinese lottery, 1938; Neg. # 17758-1 (Box 10)
  - Raid on a Chinese lottery, 1938; Neg. # 17758-2 (Box 10)
  - Raid on a Chinese lottery, 1938; Neg. # 17758-3 (Box 10)
  - Old Chinatown billboard, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1938; Neg. # 17923 (Box 11)
  - Painting a signpost in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 17924-1 (Box 11)
  - Street scene in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 17924-2 (Box 11)
  - Chop Suey restaurant in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 17924-3 (Box 11)
  - Aerial view of New Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 17924-4 (Box 11)
  - Medicine shop in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 17924-5 (Box 11)
  - Street scene in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 17925-1 (Box 11)
  - Rickshaw driver and passenger in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 17925-2 (Box 11)
  - Merchant in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 17925-3 (Box 11)
  - Community center balcony in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 18224-1 (Box 11)
  - Dragon costume in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 18224-2 (Box 11)
  - Preparing an ancestral shrine in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 18224-3 (Box 11)
  - Interior of a Chinese temple in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 18224-4 (Box 11)
  - Fortune teller in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1938; Neg. # 18224-5 (Box 11)
  - Chinese lottery and casino in Gardena (Calif.), 1938; Neg. # 18958-2 (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles slums in the Great Depression, ca. 1938; Neg. # 19164-5 (Box 12)
  - Los Angeles slums in the Great Depression, 1938; Neg. # 19164-6 (Box 12)
  - Jesse Owens runs the hurdles, ca. 1938; Neg. # 11318-2 (Box 3)
  - Henry Armstrong poses with World Featherweight Welterweight Champion robe, 1938; Neg. # 16392-1 (Box 8)
  - Kenny Washington and friends celebrate New Year's Eve, 1938; Neg. # 16567 (Box 9)
  - Mexican American women prepare food for flood victims, 1938; Neg. # 17094-1 (Box 9)
- 1939
  - Kenny Washington, portrait, ca. 1939; Neg. # 19059 (Box 12)
  - Corpus Christi Festival at Plaza Church, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1939; Neg. # 20859-4 (Box 17)
  - Inquest of the death of Faustino Sanchez, ca. 1939; Neg. # 21397-2 (Box 19)
  - Chinese temple in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1939; Neg. # 22017-1 (Box 22)
  - Dancing the jitterbug, ca. 1939; Neg. # 22336-2 (Box 24)
  - Chang Yuin-Tsung and Anna May Wong, ca. 1939; Neg. # 22442-1 (Box 25)
  - Joe Louis in the boxing ring, ca. 1939; Neg. # 22995-3 (Box 27)
  - Wishing pool in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1939; Neg. # 23690-1 (Box 32)
  - Wishing pool in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1939; Neg. # 23690-2 (Box 32)
  - Boxing, Joe Louis vs. Jack Roper, July 14, 1939; Neg. # 20315-2 (Box 14)
  - Boxing, Henry Armstrong vs. Jimmy Garrison, October 24, 1939; Neg. # 21874-1 (Box 22)
- 1940
  - Wishing pool tourists in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 23172-1 (Box 28)
  - Street scene in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 23172-3 (Box 28)
  - Interior view of a Chinatown shop, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 23172-5 (Box 28)
  - Fortune teller booth in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 23172-6 (Box 28)
  - Street scene in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 23172-7 (Box 28)
  - Restaurant in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 23172-9 (Box 28)
  - Raising the American flag for a Cinco de Mayo celebration, 1940; Neg. # 23464-1 (Box 30)
  - Nisei festival queen dines in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 24037-3 (Box 34)
  - Mayor Fletcher Bowron at a Nisei festival in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 24037-4 (Box 34)
  - Japanese immigrants register as Los Angeles residents, 1940; Neg. # 24166-51 (Box 35)
  - Japanese immigrants register as Los Angeles residents, 1940; Neg. # 24166-52 (Box 35)
  - Japanese immigrants register as Los Angeles residents, 1940; Neg. # 24166-53 (Box 35)
  - Japanese cannery workers on Terminal Island (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 24304-1 (Box 36)
  - Japanese fishermen on Terminal Island (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 24304-10 (Box 36)
  - Shinto temple on Terminal Island (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 24304-12 (Box 36)
  - Fish Harbor, Terminal Island (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 24304-2 (Box 36)
  - Japanese homes on Terminal Island (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 24304-3 (Box 36)
  - Shinto temple on Terminal Island (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 24304-4 (Box 36)
  - Terminal Island School, 1940; Neg. # 24304-5 (Box 36)
  - Mildred O. Walizer Grammar School, Terminal Island (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 24304-6 (Box 36)
  - Shinto temple on Terminal Island (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 24304-8 (Box 36)
  - Japanese homes on Terminal Island (Calif.), 1940; Neg. # 24304-9 (Box 36)
  - Major General Joseph Stilwell, portrait, ca. 1940; Neg. # 24809-1 (Box 38)
  - African American soldiers entertain at Camp Ord, Monterey Bay Peninsula (Calif.), ca. 1940; Neg. # 24809-10 (Box 38)
  - Demonstrator protests illegal raids by the Immigration Department, ca. 1940s; Neg. # 15737-1 (Box 7)
- 1941
  - United China Relief fundraising event, ca. 1941; Neg. # 26047-1 (Box 45)
  - Japanese, German, and Italian detainees, 1941; Neg. # 27021-1 (Box 51)
  - Japanese, German, and Italian detainees, 1941; Neg. # 27021-2 (Box 51)
  - Japanese, German, and Italian detainees, 1941; Neg. # 27021-3 (Box 51)
  - Japanese, German, and Italian detainees, 1941; Neg. # 27021-4 (Box 51)
  - U.S. Army soliders talk to a civilian on Terminal Island (Calif.), 1941; Neg. # 27022-3 (Box 51)
  - U.S. Army soldiers on Terminal Island (Calif.), 1941; Neg. # 27022-5 (Box 51)
  - U.S. Army soldier on duty, Terminal Island (Calif.), 1941; Neg. # 27022-8 (Box 51)
  - Members of the Japanese American Citizens' League, ca. 1941; Neg. # 27053 (Box 51)
  - U.S. Army authorities discuss Japanese American activities, 1941; Neg. # 27067-5 (Box 51)
  - FBI arrests Japanese civilians on Terminal Island (Calif.), December 7, 1941; Neg. # 27022-11 (Box 51)
  - FBI arrests Japanese civilians on Terminal Island (Calif.), December 7, 1941; Neg. # 27022-4 (Box 51)
  - Print shop in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.) on December 7, 1941, Neg. # 27027 (Box 51)
  - Reading reports of the Pearl Harbor attacks in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.), December 7, 1941; Neg. # 27027-1 (Box 51)
  - Selling newspapers in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.) on December 7, 1941, Neg. # 27027-3 (Box 51)
  - Street scene in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.) on December 7, 1941, Neg. # 27027-4 (Box 51)
  - Street scene in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.) on December 7, 1941, Neg. # 27027-5 (Box 51)
  - Street scene in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.) on December 7, 1941, Neg. # 27027-6 (Box 51)
  - Street scene in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.) on December 7, 1941, Neg. # 27027-7 (Box 51)
  - Street scene on Terminal Island (Calif.) on December 8, 1941, Neg. # 27022-10 (Box 51)
  - Street scene on Terminal Island (Calif.) on December 8, 1941, Neg. # 27022-7 (Box 51)
  - Street scene on Terminal Island (Calif.) on December 8, 1941, Neg. # 27022-9 (Box 51)
- 1942
  - Marian Anderson christens the liberty ship Booker T. Washington, 1942; Neg. # 28752-2 (Box 10)
  - Corpus Christi Festival at Plaza Church, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1942; Neg. # 20859-3 (Box 17)
  - Japanese nationals board bus for evacuation and relocation, 1942; Neg. # 27067-1 (Box 51)
  - Japanese nationals on a bus during evacuation and relocation, 1942; Neg. # 27067-2 (Box 51)
  - Japanese women board bus for evacuation and relocation, 1942; Neg. # 27067-3 (Box 51)
  - Japanese nationals board bus for evacuation and relocation, 1942; Neg. # 27067-4 (Box 51)
  - Japanese nationals on a bus during evacuation and relocation, 1942; Neg. # 27067-5 (Box 51)
  - Japanese submit personal property to the Los Angeles Police Department, ca. 1942; Neg. # 27156-1 (Box 52)
  - Japanese submit personal property to the Los Angeles Police Department, ca. 1942; Neg. # 27172 (Box 52)
  - Police officer poses with weapons submitted to the Los Angeles Police Department, 1942; Neg. # 27214-1 (Box 52)
  - A.L. Wirin speaks to striking workers, ca. 1942; Neg. # 27219-1 (Box 52)
  - Japanese agricultural workers in Burbank, California, 1942; Neg. # 27296-1 (Box 52)
  - Japanese agricultural workers in Burbank, California, 1942; Neg. # 27296-2 (Box 52)
  - Japanese immigrants register as Los Angeles residents, 1942; Neg. # 27348-1 (Box 52)
  - Japanese fisherman's cabin in Palos Verdes, California, 1942; Neg. # 27457-1 (Box 53)
  - Searching a Japanese home in Palos Verdes (Calif.), 1942; Neg. # 27457-3 (Box 53)
  - Police officials await evacuation of Japanese residents in Palos Verdes (Calif.), 1942; Neg. # 27457-4 (Box 53)
  - Searching a Japanese home in Palos Verdes (Calif.), 1942; Neg. # 27457-5 (Box 53)
  - Tom C. Clark points to notice for alien enemy prohibited territory no. 30, 1942; Neg. # 27462-1 (Box 53)
  - Notice for alien enemy prohibited territory no. 30, 1942; Neg. # 27462-2 (Box 53)
  - Japanese man with vegetables, February 1942; Neg. # 27470-6 (Box 53)
  - Police officer inspects a Japanese home on Terminal Island (Calif.), 1942; Neg. # 27492-1 (Box 53)
  - United China Relief billboard, 1942; Neg. # 27513-1 (Box 53)
  - Japanese nationals detained in a Los Angeles jail, 1942; Neg. # 27526-1 (Box 53)
  - Boxers practice in the ring, 1942; Neg. # 28121-1 (Box 56)
  - Boxer with his trainer, 1942; Neg. # 28121-2 (Box 56)
  - Boxer selects his gloves, 1942; Neg. # 28121-3 (Box 56)
  - Boxing coach advises his athletes, 1942; Neg. # 28121-4 (Box 56)
  - Teenagers read a newspaper story on Japanese submarine casualties, 1942; Neg. # 28394 (Box 58)
  - Mexican American female gang, ca. 1942; Neg. # 28443-1 (Box 58)
  - Henry Leyvas, portrait, 1942; Neg. # 28444-1 (Box 58)
  - Henry Leyvas, portrait, 1942; Neg. # 28444-2 (Box 58)
  - Sailors at a bar in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1942; Neg. # 28461-1 (Box 58)
  - Mexican consuls, ca. 1942; Neg. # 28603-1 (Box 59)
  - Mexican migrant workers travel by train to Los Angeles (Calif.), 1942; Neg. # 28737-1 (Box 60)
  - Mexican migrant workers disembark in Los Angeles (Calif.), 1942; Neg. # 28737-2 (Box 60)
  - Mexican migrant workers travel by train to Los Angeles (Calif.), 1942; Neg. # 28737-3 (Box 60)
  - Mexican migrant worker, portrait, 1942; Neg. # 28737-4 (Box 60)
  - Mexican American youths detained for questioning, ca. 1942; Neg. # 28789 (Box 60)
  - Mexican American youths detained for questioning, ca. 1942; Neg. # 28789-1 (Box 60)
  - Mexican American youths detained for questioning, ca. 1942; Neg. # 28789-2 (Box 60)
  - Mexican American youths detained for questioning, ca. 1942; Neg. # 28789-3 (Box 60)
  - Leo Carrillo surrounded by fans, ca. 1942; Neg. # 29568-1 (Box 63)
  - Luis Verdusco, seated portrait, 1942; Neg. # 29765 (Box 64)
  - Luis Verdusco, standing portrait, 1942; Neg. # 29765-1 (Box 64)
  - Japanese women prepare for evacuation from Terminal Island (Calif.), February 1942; Neg. # 27470-2 (Box 53)
  - Japanese family evacuates from Terminal Island (Calif.), February 1942; Neg. # 27470-3 (Box 53)
  - Virginia Swanson Yamamoto in front of Terminal Island Baptist Church, February 1942; Neg. # 27470-4 (Box 53)
  - Japanese man evacuates from Terminal Island (Calif.), February 1942; Neg. # 27470-5 (Box 53)
  - Japanese prepare for evacuation from Terminal Island (Calif.), February 1942; Neg. # 27470-7 (Box 53)
  - Cinco de Mayo entertainers at the Los Angeles Coliseum, May 5, 1942; Neg. # 23464-2 (Box 30)
  - Mexican Independence Day celebration, September 16, 1942; Neg. # 28675-1 (Box 59)
  - Henry Agard Wallace speaks on Mexican Independence Day, September 16, 1942; Neg. # 28675-3 (Box 59)
- 1943
  - Mexican workers move into lodgings at Whittier Ranch, Los Angeles County (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 29233 (Box 61)
  - Mexican workers move into lodgings at Whittier Ranch, Los Angeles County (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 29233-1 (Box 61)
  - Madame Chiang Kai-Shek with dignitaries at the Hollywood Bowl, 1943; Neg. # 29550-1 (Box 63)
  - Madame Chiang Kai-shek gives a speech at the Hollywood Bowl, 1943; Neg. # 29550-2 (Box 63)
  - Authorities meet to discuss the Zoot Suit Riots, 1943; Neg. # 29741 (Box 64)
  - Zoot Suit Riots, 1943; Neg. # 29765-2 (Box 64)
  - Authorities meet to discuss the Zoot Suit Riots, 1943; Neg. # 29769-1 (Box 64)
  - Wartime housing in Little Tokyo's Bronzeville, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 29954-10 (Box 64)
  - Wartime housing in the Japanese Union Church in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 29954-2 (Box 64)
  - Wartime housing in Little Tokyo's Bronzeville, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 29954-3 (Box 64)
  - Wartime housing in Little Tokyo's Bronzeville, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 29954-4 (Box 64)
  - Wartime housing in a Buddhist Temple in Little Tokyo, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 29954-5 (Box 64)
  - Wartime housing in Little Tokyo's Bronzeville, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 29954-6 (Box 64)
  - Wartime housing in Little Tokyo's Bronzeville, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 29954-7 (Box 64)
  - Wartime housing in Little Tokyo's Bronzeville, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 29954-8 (Box 64)
  - Wartime housing in Little Tokyo's Bronzeville, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 29954-9 (Box 64)
  - Authorities meet to discuss the Zoot Suit Riots, 1943; Neg. # 30477-2 (Box 65)
  - Chinese funeral in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1943; Neg. # 30704-2 (Box 66)
  - Hollywood fundraiser for the Sleepy Lagoon defense fund, ca. 1943; Neg. # 30709-1 (Box 66)
- 1944
  - Belvedere Grammar School play, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1944; Neg. # 31515-51 (Box 69)
  - A.L. Wirin, George Ochikubo, and Saburo Kido, ca. 1944; Neg. # 32085 (Box 71)
  - Sleepy Lagoon murder case acquittal, October 1944; Neg. # 32252-7 (Box 72)
  - Carlos Chávez, portrait, 1944; Neg. # 32565-1 (Box 73)
  - Ransacked Japanese warehouse in Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1944; Neg. # 32732-501 (Box 74)
  - Cinco de Mayo celebration at Los Angeles City Hall, May 5, 1944; Neg. # 31531-1 (Box 69)
  - Sleepy Lagoon murder case acquittal, October 1944; Neg. # 32252 (Box 72)
  - Sleepy Lagoon murder case acquittal, October 1944; Neg. # 32252-1 (Box 72)
  - Sleepy Lagoon murder case acquittal, October 1944; Neg. # 32252-2 (Box 72)
  - Sleepy Lagoon murder case acquittal, October 1944; Neg. # 32252-3 (Box 72)
  - Telles family at the Sleepy Lagoon murder case acquittal, October 1944; Neg. # 32252-4 (Box 72)
  - Sleepy Lagoon murder case acquittal, October 1944; Neg. # 32252-5 (Box 72)
  - Telles family at the Sleepy Lagoon murder case acquittal, October 1944; Neg. # 32252-6 (Box 72)
- 1945
  - Augustus F. Hawkins and John Anson Ford, 1945; Neg. # 33982 (Box 78)
  - Demonstrators rest during a discriminatory housing protest in Los Angeles (Calif.), 1945; Neg. # 34530-4 (Box 81)
  - Japanese return from internment camps, November 5, 1945; Neg. # 34364 (Box 80)
  - Japanese return from internment camps, November 5, 1945; Neg. # 34364-2 (Box 80)
- 1946
  - Kenny Washington receives a football award, ca. 1946; Neg. # 44050-2 (Box 129)
  - Edward Roybal sworn in as Los Angeles City Council member, 1946; Neg. # 46149 (Box 137)
  - Demonstrators protest discriminatory housing in Los Angeles (Calif.), 1946; Neg. # 34530-1 (Box 81)
  - Demonstrators protest discriminatory zoning at Los Angeles City Hall, 1946; Neg. # 34659 (Box 81)
  - Gus Arriola poses with admirers, 1946; Neg. # 35302-2 (Box 84)
  - Robert Walker Kenny with a man in Ku Klux Klan costume, ca. 1946; Neg. # 35397-1 (Box 85)
  - Temporary Japanese post-war housing, 1946; Neg. # 35934-1 (Box 86)
  - Japanese American children in temporary post-war housing, 1946; Neg. # 35934-3 (Box 86)
  - Temporary Japanese post-war housing, 1946; Neg. # 35934-5 (Box 86)
  - Temporary Japanese post-war housing, 1946; Neg. # 35934-6 (Box 86)
  - Ku Klux Klan cross burning incident, ca. 1946; Neg. # 36019 (Box 87)
  - Temporary Japanese post-war housing, 1946; Neg. # 36081-1 (Box 87)
  - Temporary Japanese post-war housing, 1946; Neg. # 36081-2 (Box 87)
  - Temporary Japanese post-war housing, 1946; Neg. # 36081-3 (Box 87)
  - Temporary Japanese post-war housing, 1946; Neg. # 36081-4 (Box 87)
  - Posting a sign regarding bus service to Chavez Ravine in Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1946; Neg. # 36414 (Box 89)
  - Hillside view of Chavez Ravine, 1946; Neg. # 36414-1 (Box 89)
  - Bus terminal in Chavez Ravine, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1946; Neg. # 36414-2 (Box 89)
  - Bus terminal store in Chavez Ravine, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1946; Neg. # 36414-3 (Box 89)
  - Women walk the road into Chavez Ravine, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1946; Neg. # 36414-4 (Box 89)
  - Pan American Day celebration, April 14, 1946; Neg. # 35520-1 (Box 85)
  - Mexican Independence Day celebration, September 16, 1946; Neg. # 36725-1 (Box 91)
  - Mexican Independence Day celebration, September 16, 1946; Neg. # 36725-3 (Box 91)
  - Decorating a float for the Tournament of Roses, December 1946; Neg. # 34611-3 (Box 81)
- 1947
  - Dedication of a plaque at Rancho Los Cerritos, Long Beach, California, 1947; Neg. # 40035-3 (Box 107)
  - Communion at Plaza Church, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1947; Neg. # 40911-1 (Box 112)
  - Interior view of Plaza Church, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1947; Neg. # 40911-2 (Box 112)
  - Altar of Plaza Church, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1947; Neg. # 40911-3 (Box 112)
  - Street scene in Chavez Ravine, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1947; Neg. # 36414-5 (Box 89)
  - Hitchhiking sailors outside the Naval and Marine Training Center, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1947; Neg. # 36414-6 (Box 89)
  - Slim Gaillard, portrait, ca. 1947; Neg. # 38202 (Box 98)
  - Eslanda Goode Robeson, portrait, ca. 1947; Neg. # 38261-1 (Box 98)
- 1948
  - Mexican American male gang, ca. 1948; Neg. # 41148-1 (Box 114)
  - Chinese funeral in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1948; Neg. # 41213-1 (Box 114)
  - Costumes for a fiesta on Olvera Street, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1948; Neg. # 41286-1 (Box 114)
  - Reenactment of the 1769 Gaspar de Portolá expedition, 1948; Neg. # 42844-2 (Box 123)
  - Reenactment of the 1769 Gaspar de Portolá expedition, 1948; Neg. # 42844-4 (Box 123)
  - Reenactment of the 1769 Gaspar de Portolá expedition, 1948; Neg. # 42844-5 (Box 123)
- 1949
  - Los Angeles residents raise funds for flood victims in Sonora, Mexico, 1949; Neg. # 44795 (Box 132)
  - Joseph S. Saldana, portrait, 1949; Neg. # 45066-1 (Box 133)
  - Dragon parade in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1949; Neg. # 45872-2 (Box 136)
  - Ralph Bunche Day declared in Los Angeles (Calif.), 1949; Neg. # 46313-1 (Box 138)
  - NAACP convention in Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1949; Neg. # 46363-1 (Box 138)
  - Roy Wilkins speaks at an NAACP convention, Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1949; Neg. # 46363-4 (Box 138)
  - Four Families Association building in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1949; Neg. # 46439-1 (Box 139)
  - Four Families Association building in Chinatown, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1949; Neg. # 46439-2 (Box 139)
  - Boxer practices in the ring, 1949; Neg. # 46623-1 (Box 139)
  - Paul Robeson and Charlotta Bass, ca. 1949; Neg. # 47089 (Box 141)
  - Gus Arriola draws cartoons for children, ca. 1949; Neg. # 47742-2 (Box 144)
  - Woodrow Wilson Strode registers for military service, ca. 1940; Neg. # 24469-3 (Box 36)
  - Tourists on Olvera Street, Los Angeles (Calif.), 1949; Neg. # 36412-1 (Box 89)
  - Paul Robeson awaits testimony before the Committee of Un-American Activities, ca. 1949; Neg. # 36937-1 (Box 92)
- 1950
  - March of Dimes parade in Los Angeles (Calif.), ca. 1950; Neg. # 44364-1 (Box 127)
  - Richard Gonzales plays a tennis match, ca. 1950; Neg. # 46959-1 (Box 141)
  - Boxing, Art Aragon vs. Bobby Campbell, ca. 1950; Neg. # 50578-1 (Box 150)
  - Exhibition soccer, Mexico vs. Great Britain, 1950; Neg. # 50610-2 (Box 151)
  - Art Aragon, portrait, ca. 1950; Neg. # 51131 (Box 152)
  - Paul Younger's military physical exam, ca. 1950; Neg. # 51224-1 (Box 152)
  - Lugo family members, ca. 1950; Neg. # 51322 (Box 153)
  - View under bridge towards Chavez Ravine's "Lil' Town", 1950; Neg. # 52406 (Box 156)